Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ gianpaolograzioli (LinkedIn) www.giapo.com (Company)

Top Skills

Social Media Team Leadership Event Management

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
Italian (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

The Cuisine Artisan Award
The Cuisine Popular Choice Award

Publications

Effect of music genre on pleasantness of three types of chocolate gelati

Gianpaolo Grazioli

Gianpaolo

New Zealand

Summary

Haere Mai, my name is Giapo Grazioli, I am the chef and patron at Giapo Ice Cream.

During these years running the kitchen at Giapo I saw that Ice Cream had the potential to be more expressive than what it had been so far. In my mind ice cream had to carry a different narrative.

I focused my kitchen work on mashing up ideas from all the humanities including technology, art and science. I am currently doing scientific research with AUT and Otago University. I run a blog where I write about my kitchen observations and I am the co-author of a few published peer-reviewed papers.

Come down to Giapo Ice Cream to try one of my creations at 12 Gore st, Auckland, New Zealand.

To find out more visit: www.giapo.com

Experience

Cherlato
Chief Executive Officer
April 2023 - Present (1 year 11 months)
Los Angeles, California, United States

GIAPO

Head Chef February 2007 - Present (18 years 1 month)

Auckland

http://www.giapo.com/

Melior Hospitality
Pastry Chef / Catering
February 2006 - May 2008 (2 years 4 months)

Pasticceria Santa Croce Assistant Pastry Chef June 2002 - January 2004 (1 year 8 months)

Torre del Greco

Education

Auckland University of Technology
Applied Science, Food Science · (2010 - 2011)

London Metropolitan University
CCOS, Commercial operation and shipping · (2001 - 2002)

Università degli Studi di Napoli 'Parthenope' Bachelor of Commerce (BCom), International Economics · (1997 - 2001)